// Questions array 

const QUESTIONS_ARRAY = {
    // Array for the sporst quiz
    'rock': [
             {
                  question: 'WWhat British rock band pioneered the use of the light show?',
                  choice1: 'Led Zeppelin',
                  choice2: 'the Beatles',
                  choice3: 'Pink Floyd',
                  choice4: 'Lynyrd Skynyrd',
                  correctAnswer: 3
                },
                {
                  question: 'This British rock group debuted with their album "Mr. Fantasy" (1967):?',
                  choice1: 'Derek and the Dominos',
                  choice2: 'The Blur',
                  choice3: 'Adam and the Ants',
                  choice4: 'Traffic',
                  correctAnswer: 4
                },
                {
                  question: 'Which rock band was formed in 1985 by Rose and Stradlin?',
                  choice1: 'Guns & Roses',
                  choice2: 'Aerosmith',
                  choice3: 'Nirvana',
                  choice4: 'The Eagles',
                  correctAnswer: 1
                },
                  {
                  question: 'Which instrument did Jimi Hendrix play?',
                  choice1: 'Piano',
                  choice2: 'Drum',
                  choice3: 'Electric Guitar',
                  choice4: 'Saxophone',
                  correctAnswer: 3
                },
                  {
                  question: 'Which funk style originated in Washington in the 1970s?',
                  choice1: 'G-funk',
                  choice2: 'Go-go',
                  choice3: 'Afrobeat',
                  choice4: 'Avant-funk',
                  correctAnswer: 2
                },
                {
                  question: 'The famous British rock group Led Zeppelin was initially known as:',
                  choice1: 'The Black Album',
                  choice2: 'Acca Dacca',
                  choice3: 'Hollywood Rose',
                  choice4: 'The New Yardbirds',
                  correctAnswer: 4
                },
                {
                  question: 'Which member of the Beatles was known as â€œthe quiet Beatle"?',
                  choice1: 'George Harrison',
                  choice2: 'John Lennon',
                  choice3: 'Ringo Starr',
                  choice4: 'Pete Best',
                  correctAnswer: 1
                },
                {
                  question: 'What are the instruments in a classic three-piece rock band?',
                  choice1: 'Guitar, violin, drums',
                  choice2: 'Guitar, bass, trumpet',
                  choice3: 'Guitar, bass, drums',
                  choice4: 'Guitar, organ, drums',
                  correctAnswer: 3
                },
                {
                  question: 'The song "Born in the U.S.A." (1984) is associated with which singer?',
                  choice1: 'Clarence Clemons',
                  choice2: 'Bruce Springsteen',
                  choice3: 'Steven Van Zandt',
                  choice4: 'Billy Joel',
                  correctAnswer: 2
                },
                {
                  question: 'In which year did Psychedelic rock emerge?',
                  choice1: '1971',
                  choice2: '1975',
                  choice3: '1963',
                  choice4: '1966',
                  correctAnswer: 4
                }
            
    ],
    
};  